Dammit!
Over here!
Ow, ow, ow!
Come on, you two, stop it!
Taichi!
Inaba? Did you find him?
I couldn't.
Dammit, where'd he go?
Where'd he go?
He go!
Going somewhere with a lot of people might have been a mistake...
We said we'd go to the shrine on New Year's as the CRC last year, didn't we?
Didn't we?
Din' we!
Shut up, you little brats!
Inaba Nee-chan!
I bought some takoyaki!
Maybe you should've told me before you bought them!
Well, that doesn't matter now.
Taichi.
Come on. Open your mouth.
You've got your hands full.
Not really. I can let go...
Oh, sorry.
What a coincidence, Inaba-san, Yaegashi-kun.
And Happy New Year.
Fujishima...
Why are you two paying a shrine visit together?
Who are those kids?
They're relatives, you know? Uh...
We said we were going to the shrine as the CRC, and they dumped these kids on us.
Yeah, yeah. That's what happened.
Oh?
This girl looks an awful lot like Nagase-san.
Like if Nagase-san went back to being a kid.
Oh, sorry! We have to go now!
Huh? Hey, wait—
Where are we going?
It doesn't matter. Come on.
Hey, I want one of these!
Why'd it turn out like this?
I'll get you one later!
For a while after the whole "desire unleashing" thing,
we were able to live our lives in peace.
I haven't resolved the whole issue with Inaba and Nagase,
but nothing's changed between us since then.
But on the last day of school before winter break...
What's this?
It was on there when we got here.
But no one here knows who wrote it.
It's almost 12...
What's wrong, Nagase?
My body feels hot...
I'm hot, too!
What's this?
Flop! Flop! Flop!
Hey! Snacks!
Can I have some?
Y-Yeah...
Yay!
Let's eat them together.
Okay!
What's going on?
I don't know.
Is there something wrong with my eyes?
Something wrong with my eyes?
That has to be it!
Okay, I'll close my eyes.
When I open them, everything will be normal again.
One, two, three, open!
Still not normal!
What the hell?!
Then I'll ask again.
What's your name, and how old are you?
Okay!
Kiriyama Yui! I'm eleven!
Nagase Iori. Six.
Okay, next question.
Who's this lanky guy with the dirty mind here?
Aoki-san.
Aoki Onii-chan.
You don't need to say "dirty mind"!
Then who's this kind of handsome guy here?
Taichi-san.
Taichi Onii-chan.
And I get a compliment, Inaba-san?
So, do you two know why you're here?
Nope.
And there we have it.
What the hell do we have here?! This makes no sense!
So Nagase and Kiriyama got younger?
Yeah.
They're back to the way they were as kids.
They don't know why or how they got here,
but they do have a vague idea of what's going on around them,
so they don't have any problems with it.
Though they don't really get it.
Or something like that.
You think it's Balloon Vine again?
That's the only possibility I can see.
Maybe...
They're back!
What?
Huh?
What's my skirt doing up this high?!
Iori-chan...
We're here, too...
Then don't look!
So we can probably call it "time regression" this time.
Do you remember anything from when you turned into a kid?
No, I don't.
But my memories from then feel kind of fresh in my mind.
Like playing with friends and going to school,
and stuff at home.
For me, it's what I was like back in fifth grade.
I was so bright and breezy.
It makes me kind of sad now.
And winter break starts tomorrow.
What if we turn into kids in front of our families?
It said twelve to five on the board.
If it only happens between those times,
we might be able to deal with it if we can find somewhere to hide.
For now, that writing on the blackboard's all we can go by.
There's a building scheduled for demolition by my house.
Let's meet there tomorrow.
I'm ho—
Onii-chan, what took you?
Sorry. I have stuff I need to do, too.
Something more important than your cute little sister?
Well, it is Christmas, and you do have a girlfriend.
I'm sure you have a lot of stuff to do.
I told you, I don't have a girlfriend.
Well, we came close to being in a situation like that,
but now's not the time for that, or something like that...
Don't tell me you didn't give her a present.
I'm telling you, it's complicated.
Wait, hold on, Onii-chan!
Balloon Vine?
Yes.
Balloon Vine.
But not.
You can call me The Second.
What do you mean?
Are you Balloon Vine or not?
I am Balloon Vine,
but not the Balloon Vine you know.
So I'm The Second.
So you're part of Balloon Vine's ilk,
but you're not him.
I want you to be a knight.
Knight?
If you all turn into kids, it'll be bad.
There's no way to deal with that.
Your job is to make sure nothing bad happens.
I'll... watch.
It won't be too long.
But don't tell anyone about me.
If you do...
I'll make twelve to five into forever.
What do you mean?!
How are you related to Balloon Vine?!
What was I doing just now?
Did I really turn completely into a kid?
Yeah, I think.
Okay, then...
Do you think Taichi won't like me anymore now that he's seen me as a kid?
He's not that kind of person.
I think.
Yeah, you're right. I think.
What is with this conversation?
It's weird enough that we'd talk about something like this,
but when we love the same person, too?
This has to be a joke.
Seriously.
I never thought a day would come when I'd talk about this with you.
Oh, my mom's back home.
Bye, Inaban. See you tomorrow.
Yeah, see—
No way! Why'd you quit?
Some... stuff happened.
But what about our promise?
Promise?
Yeah, our promise!
That promise we made!
Taichi.
Hey. A friend of yours?
Yeah. Mihashi Chinatsu-san.
A friend from back when I practiced karate.
This is Yaegashi Taichi-kun.
What, your boyfriend?
No, we're just on our way to a friend's house.
He's not my boyfriend.
Yeah. Really.
He's absolutely, positively not my boyfriend.
I think she gets the picture.
Sorry, we're in a hurry, so see you!
Wait, Kiriyama...
I'll never accept this, Kiriyama!
I went up against Mihashi-san in a lot of tournaments.
She's more like a rival than a friend.
A rival?
That's pretty crazy.
That's the kind of world you were in...
Yeah, back in the day.
But I haven't seen her since she moved away,
and I stopped practicing karate.
She said something about a promise?
Yeah.
But I don't remember.
I'm perfectly fine. How are you doing there?
I see.
I'll be home as soon as I can.
Nagase.
Taichi! Yui! Morning!
Why are you together?
Taichi, don't tell me you're going to take down Yui now that you've got Inaban!
Now that he's got Inaban? What?
N-Nothing, Kiriyama!
Hey, this place is pretty nice.
You really think someone's going to turn into a kid today?
I still can't really believe it...
Fire!
No way!
What happened?!
She's too cute!
You can see the resemblance to the cool beauty she'll be in the future,
but she still has that cuteness that only kids have!
It's too much!
Just thinking that this is Inaban...
I have to have her!
Shouldn't you be panicking?
Girls are scary...
I'm stuffed...
My cuteium reserves are fully charged now...
You two need to learn some self-control.
Now she's totally afraid of you.
I do feel bad about it...
Same here.
Sorry about that, Himeko-chan.
N-No!
I can't let myself experience what Nagase and Kiriyama just did!
Himeko-chan, what do you want to drink?
Orange.
Okay. Here you go.
Wait, one second...
Here.
Thank you.
I want cola!
Here you go.
Yay!
Thanks, Nana's sister!
Nana?
You're Nana's sister, right?
Aren't you?
Who's that?
Yoshifumi-kun, do you know my full name?
Yaegashi Taichi-san.
Then what about hers?
Nagase Iori-san.
She isn't Nishino Nana's big sister?
Um...
I'm Kiriyama Yui...
Kiriyama Yui?
Oh, right.
You look just like her...
Very good, Himeko-chan!
You can already write your own name!
That's amazing!
You can see Inaba's brilliant mind already taking shape!
There! I win!
I'm faster than you!
Dang!
What were you two doing?
Exploring the building.
And a race.
I won!
You're so immature! That's why you haven't kissed anyone!
I-I said that I've kissed before!
What were you talking about?!
I mean, sure, I was Inaban at the time, but...
But it was me inside there, so that was my first kiss!
I've decided!
N-Nagase, don't say any more...
Should I have just heard that?
What's a kiss?
You're too young for this, Himeko-chan!
This is grown-up talk!
Will I be a grown-up if I kiss?
It's not really like that...
It's more like something you do when you're a grown-up...
When will I kiss?
At the latest, the fall of your first year in high—
That doesn't matter right now!
Oh, right. What about clothes?
Huh?
I mean, what happens to our clothes when we go back to normal?
They stay on you, so...
Crap!
They need to change clothes, now!
Taichi, move!
Got it!
Come on, Himeko-chan.
What am I supposed to do?
Hurry!
For now, turn around and close your eyes!
Yeah, that works.
You too, Yoshifumi-kun!
Oh no! We won't make it!
It hurts!
These clothes are too tight!
What the hell?!
Why am I naked?!
I-I-I-Inaban!
Stop, stop, stop!
So I was ten years old?
Not having any memories of those five hours is way too disturbing.
It looks like the blackboard really was a clue from Balloon Vine.
Then having only four of our names on the board must mean something.
Maybe Taichi won't get time regressed?
Balloon Vine'll probably show himself and explain all this soon enough, but it's taking him way too long.
Hey, whose is this? Can I drink it?
Hey, quick question.
Do you know someone named Nishino Nana?
Wait, Yui, how do you know about her?
When you were ten years old, you thought that I was Nishino Nana's big sister.
You said I looked just like her.
She was a girl who lived near me. We're the same age.
I dated her in my first year of middle school.
But at the end of that first year, Nana had to move.
Since then, all we've done is exchange New Year's cards.
Something like that.
Do you think she'd look like me if she were in high school?
I think, maybe.
Isn't that like...
You... weren't acting like yourself back there.
I thought you would say something like,
"But that doesn't matter! I love you!"
Just on the spur of the moment.
You haven't had a time regression yet, so you don't know,
but your memories from back then feel really fresh in your mind.
It's confusing the heck out of me.
Confusing the heck out of you?
I mean, I remember how much I loved Nana back then.
I can't say I didn't.
I love Yui.
But back then, I was in love with Nana.
Then when did I stop loving Nana?
Is it gone forever?
Or is it still there?
Hey, Taichi...
What does it mean to love someone?
Onee?
What is it?
What happened?
You hated looking at those things ever since you stopped practicing karate.
Nothing. I was just remembering a few things from the past.
Oh, right. I ran into Mihashi-san today.
Here, this girl.
I talked to her quite a bit back then.
She said she was staying with some relatives in town right now.
Though it's only for winter break.
Oh?
Onee, why'd you stop practicing karate?
I loved how cool you looked back when you did karate.
Onee?
What's wrong?
Did I say something bad?
Sorry!
Don't cry, Onee...
Nagase.
Taichi!
What a coincidence!
We're headed to the same place,
so of course we'd run into each other.
Taichi, can I ask you a favor?
What is it?
You don't need to look too deep,
but could you pay attention to how I was as a kid?
Like, what kind of kid I was.
You mean, you want to know what kind of person you were back then?
No, no.
I don't really want to think too hard about that.
But when you're actually in a situation like this, it's hard not to think about it.
If you had a chance to relive your past,
would you do something different, Taichi?
There are a lot of times that I think "If only I'd done that," but...
If I could relive mine, I think I'd do things differently.
And if I could do things better, I'd want to do them better.
Aoki Yoshifumi, eleven!
Nagase Iori, fourteen.
It's really cold outside!
Want to wear my gloves, Iori-chan?
Don't worry about me, Taichi-san.
No need to be reserved.
Here.
Thank you very much.
They're so warm!
Now, don't you look happy.
Then as thanks...
I love you, Onii-chan!
"O-Onii-chan"?!
I thought you liked being called "Onii-chan," Taichi-san.
Well, I do... but how did you know?!
A woman's intuition, I guess.
How frightening!
Is this how Nagase was back when she would change her personality to what people around her wanted?
How long are you going to keep grinning like an idiot,
"Onii-chan"?
My, you're in perfect sync!
You're almost like boyfriend and girlfriend!
Taichi and me look like boyfriend and girlfriend?
Yes.
I-I see!
You're a good kid, Iori-chan.
All right!
I'll buy you something you want later!
Thank you very much!
Don't mention it!
What should I get?
She's even got Inaba under her thumb...
Anything you want!
Then why don't we get something that everyone can enjoy?
Is this the real fourteen-year-old Nagase Iori?
Is that what Nagase calls "changing her personality depending on the situation"?
By the way, what was I like when I was a kid?
Was I as shy as I remember?
You were afraid of Nagase and Kiriyama,
but that was their fault...
You're right.
I was always afraid of something.
And I still am.
Everyone has something they don't want others to know.
There are things you're better off not knowing.
And maybe there are things you're better off not remembering about yourself.
But in this phenomenon, our past selves appear in complete form in the present.
One day, it might be the trigger for something that ruins us all.
We've been able to get through things together so far.
So this time...
I'm scared, Taichi.
I'm scared.
I told you...
I don't remember making any promise!
Hey, quit shaking.
Has your mom asked you anything about it?
Aoki, do you not love Yui anymore?
I... forgot to be laid-back!